let quiz   =[
    {question: "What is the double of 7 ? ",
option:[
    14,
    13,
    21,
    23,

],
answer:1, 
},

{
    question: "What is the half of 12 ? ",
option:[
    5,
    7,
    6.5,
    6,

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Subtact:25 - 5 =__? ",
option:[
    19,
    20,
    21,
    23,

],
answer:2, 
},
{question: "Find the missing number in this sequence. 5,__,15,20,25. ",
option:[
    12,
    13,
    10,
    9,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "which sentence is true? 15-1=13 ,13+5=9 ,12+1=11 ,14-1=13.",
option:[
    "13+5=9",
    "15-1=13",
    "12+1=11",
    "14-1=13",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: " ('62 __ 71')  Which sign makes this statement true? > < = ",
option:[
    "=",
    ">",
    "<",
    "None of these",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "Add: 19+0=___?",
option:[
    19,
    10,
    18,
    20,

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "Find the missing numbers. 18=__tens+__ones.",
option:[
    "10tens+8ones",
    "8tens+1ones",
    "1tens+8ones",
    "None of these",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "Find the missing number in this sequence. 4,8,12,___,20.",
option:[
    17,
    16,
    18,
    20,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "What is the double of 12?",
option:[
    24,
    23,
    22,
    25,

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "Add: 25+5=___?",
option:[
    20,
    27,
    31,
    30,

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Find the missing numbers. 21=__tens+__ones",
option:[
    "20tens+1ones",
    "2tens+1ones",
    "1tens+2ones",
    "None of these",

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "Subtact:15-5 =__? ",
option:[
    11,
    10,
    15,
    20,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "What is the half of 8?",
option:[
    4.5,
    5,
    5.5,
    4,

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "How do you write this number using digit? 'TWELVE'",
option:[
    11,
    13,
    10,
    12,

],
answer:4, 
}]  